Guys, I forgot I started the stream.
I'm not even kidding.
I started the stream, I went to the living room, I got a drink, and I was on my phone, and I started scrolling, and I completely forgot.
I'm not even joking with you.
That is fucked up.
How long was I gone?
Wait, how long was I gone?
You can't have been waiting long though, right?
Two minutes.
Okay, okay.
Well, that's fine.
That's fine.
Christ, man.
That may be the worst case of, you know, call it what you will.
Anyway, I got the drink as well.
Cheers.
Why is the background shaking?
What?
I don't know.
I think... Are you sure you're not shaking?
Is there an earthquake outside your window?
Shaking your monitor, maybe?
Nah, it's not shaking, guys.
Nah, it's not.
It's not shaking.
Not for me.
Guys, come on.
You think you can gaslight me?
Nah, bro.
God damn!
I'm ready to play some Isaac.
And you know what?
I think it's time we give the challenges some love.
The challenges have been left behind for too long.
And greed mode.
We gotta catch up on that too.
Are you ready though?
I am ready.
I was born for this.
There we go.
Okay, switch it up.
Let's see here.
You can't see anything?
Now you can?
Boom.
Challenges.
I can't stand the fact that I haven't unlocked 8 and 11.
It is actually really annoying me.
But let's do the family man, I guess.
The family man.
Oh, I see.
I'm dad.
I got dad's key.
I got big ass ears.
And I got 3 kits.
Shit.
That's rough.
I have to remember all the keybinds here.
That's sister Maggie.
Brother Bobby, rotten baby.
Okay, okay.
Can I fire?
Oh, I can't.
Wait, what does the rotten baby do?
Generates blue flies, okay.
Well, so this is pretty much just like playing Yulith.
Except we have a key.
That's cool, I guess.
It's not really gonna be a challenge though, is it?
Come on now.
Nah, it's probably gonna be difficult.
We'll see.
I do a respectable amount of damage.
Dude, it is so weird playing this game again.
I haven't played this in a while.
I gotta get used to the controls and all that.
If I'm not doing so well, it's because of that, okay?
I have an excuse all lined up.
Oh, we got golden poop.
That means we don't have to think about money.
We're good on that one.
Oh, it's a good one too!
Sick.
That's 12 coins, baby.
We're not doing boss yet.
Oh my god.
That was a little bit scary there.
I may actually go into the curse room.
Box of friends.
Ooh, that's really good for me.
Yo, duplicating.
Now we're really playing Yulith.
I think I should do it.
I told you I was Yulith.
But is there anything I can use my key on before I do?
Is there really nothing?
That can't be right.
Okay, more money.
Now we can grab this heart.
There's also another heart somewhere.
Yeah, we can get full HP.
That's awesome.
So I can also buy a pill, actually.
Yeah, let's do it.
Nice!
Fuck yeah, dude.
I love pills.
It's my favorite.
This game is easy.
Easy.
All according to script.
I was drinking.
Hold on.
Did I get you there?
Simulated drinking.
I wasn't drinking at all.
Acting.
I don't know why I even said that doesn't make any sense.
I mean, I'm doing good damage here.
I don't even know who this guy is.
Get him out of here.
Brain worm, missed shots turned 90 degrees to target enemies.
Does that work for my little dudes?
Increase random stats.
Ooh, we lost an HP.
But we gained damage.
Actually, I'm fine with that.
I'm okay.
Yeah, man.
More damage from me.
Burning basement.
We're going angel mode.
Obviously.
Oh, wait, I can't get to the... Actually, wait, wait.
Do we have a... No, okay.
I was looking for a tinted rock.
I could somehow combo.
God damn it.
Okay.
That could come in handy.
Wait, what is the difference between the red and the blue baby, actually?
Basic tiers.
Six damage is kind of sick.
But lower rate of fire, I see.
I see how it is.
That's the difference.
It's going to be tough, guys.
I may take damage here.
Nevermind.
Went better than expected.
Oh, crap.
Whoa.
Actually, pretty good at AOE.
Crowd control is top notch.
We also have the box ready in case we need it.
I'm not going to waste the key on that.
I got no money.
Yeah, let's just keep going.
We got to get to the boss ASAP.
Yeah, the red baby does a lot of damage.
And look at this.
Buffer baby.
Well, not a buffer baby, but you know, buffer baby expression.
Oh, masterfully done.
I still got it, man.
I didn't lose any skills.
In fact, I may have gained skills.
Hey.
Want a piece of me?
No drops for me.
That was kind of close.
Tonsil.
After taking damage a bunch of times, spawns a tonsil familiar that block shots.
After a second tonsil is spawned, the trinket is destroyed.
No.
Also, I don't think... Also, what I mean to say is, I don't know if my babies are actually adhering to my trinket.
Oh, that was a tinted rock.
I got to try and pay attention to the...
to the shots that are missing.
Because if it's not working, I may as well take the tonsil.
Oh, no.
Hate that room.
Okay, let me miss on purpose.
Oh, wait.
They're not actually... whatever.
Honestly, I don't think it's working.
Oh, my God.
Another one, dude.
We are so ready.
Okay, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna take this because I don't think it's working.
Oh, there's a tinted rock in there, too.
What the heck, man?
Why there's so many?
Sick.
Flavor text.
This is gonna be a tough one.
He's pushing.
Okay, good.
Thank God.
What?
Huh?
He was altering its route.
It's fine, though.
The red baby is actually kind of broken.
Another tinted rock.
But I don't have any bombs left.
That's a rip.
This one's gonna be easy.
We're gonna duplicate the shit out of this one.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah.
You like that?
Jesus Christ.
Catenine tails.
Lovely.
You know what?
I have so many blue hearts.
Maybe it makes sense to grab the demons.
Guys, I'm going demon.
What's that?
Oh, that's a new one.
Wait, what?
Bloodlust, rage.
Grants a stacking damage bonus each time Isaac takes damage.
Maximum of six stacks.
Damage bonus resets when entering a new floor.
Oh, I don't like that.
I would need some kind of build where taking damage kind of heals me or something.
Otherwise, that's bad.
Or you get the mantle if that counts.
Maybe it doesn't count, actually.
Grants a small damage for each coin held.
This will depend on the amount of money I'll find.
It's probably not worth.
Does that actually... No, take it.
I feel it.
I'm feeling it.
I'm also gonna go and check out the curse room.
I'm going all in right now.
No expenses spared.
And maybe the shop as well, actually.
Because maybe the shop has like a bomb I can buy, right?
Oh, no.
Okay, well, nice.
That may actually have been worth it.
I'll check out the shop.
I guess a buffer also destroy these fires.
We gotta stay buffed up for the next floor.
Okay, now I'm ready.
We're gonna destroy that tinted rock and then we do the boss.
No, my boss is done.
We move on.
Here's on that one.
Don't get hit.
Boom.
Nice.
I got buffers for days.
I think it's going pretty well.
Good run so far.
Now I think I want to stack up my money.
Catacombs.
I do wonder though if my getting damage ups actually helps me.
I think the red baby may be a situation of powerful early on, falls off later.
Static damage of six, you know.
The tick... Actually, yes.
I like that.
I kind of hate the tonsil.
Sick.
Box is ready too.
Don't need it.
No bombs though.
Still haven't found a secret room at all.
Nevermind.
Give
me bombs.
Okay, that's good.
More damage for me.
See, this is why I love Spidermod as well.
You can see the damage you do.
I can see whether or not my shit actually works when I get it, you know.
Yet another common Spidermod W.
Okay, I don't need that.
We're gonna do this.
Nevermind.
Got no bombs, Captain.
This was a questionable one.
Yeah, I knew that was gonna happen, man.
But hey, I'm getting damage every time I take damage, right?
Well, that's something I guess.
Oh, one shot that guy right there.
Still no bombs.
Wait, is it actually a good idea though?
It's cheap.
Ah, man, I need my box.
I can use it once.
That's also very good.
I feel like I need my buffer here.
No, I need to keep my money.
I have money equals power.
Let's just not buy anything yet.
Don't think about it.
Boss detected.
You're gonna die so fast.
How come I can't damage?
Oh, you gotta hit it from behind.
I'm just shooting and hoping for the best.
I'm not really aiming.
Nice.
HP, please.
Shit.
That's practically useless for me.
Wait, let me see.
No, that's nothing for me.
That's crazy.
I guess we're committed to demons now.
I don't mind it, honestly.
Okay, so what do we have here?
We have this thing I like a lot, actually.
Dry baby.
Blocks, enemy shots, chance to deal instant.
Ooh, that's pretty good as well.
But I only have two red hearts.
Oh my god.
That's rough.
Blocks, enemy shots.
Ah, man, I'm gonna have to leave him.
I can't, I can't, I gotta play it conservatively.
I can't do it.
Um, let's go to the curse room.
Come on, then.
Ooh, nice!
Great buffer.
Okay, well, do we have a stepper?
Kinda wanna step now.
Ah, well, actually, not really.
I have a buffer.
Dude, I actually have insane damage.
Okay, what am I missing here?
We got this thing I don't want.
Tick is good.
I could grab this.
See what I get.
Okay.
More damage.
And secret room has been found.
I think we're done here.
Maybe I check out the shop now that I have 15 coins.
There was something else in there that I perhaps wanted to buy.
But I gotta look at it again.
Oh, oh wait, we can also...
Oh, wait, the best way to do this... Can I somehow... If I do, like, right here... No, I can't, I actually can't, I have to do this.
We gotta use both bombs.
Nice!
Beautiful.
More money.
Just wonderful.
Ah, we can get the nightlight.
We can actually, I guess I can buy this and use it once.
Ooh, if I use this once, I can use one of the hearts to trade in the... in the demon room.
Ooh, wait.
Wait, wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Is it even open?
It's probably close to this point.
Right?
Yeah, okay, okay.
It was a good idea, though.
Okay, I'm gonna take nightlights.
I'll take this.
Wait, I miscalculated!
I needed to use converter once.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, we gotta find one more coin.
No, one more coin.
You gotta be beshiddling me.
Uh, what has coins normally?
Uh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Fuck!
There's no coins!
Please be coins.
Nah, man.
Shit.
Okay, this guy!
We're back!
You thought I was out?
No way.
I always come back.
Yoink!
Boom!
Okay, wait, we have a battery as well, but I can't reach it, unfortunately.
Now I grab this and move on.
That was good, that was good!
I like it!
An extra heart there is... beautiful.
Dude, I kind of want to grab the converter and keep it.
Because honestly... Oh, think about it!
Guys, the more we convert, the more red hearts we have.
Red hearts are good, because you can heal up again.
And we are all about taking damage.
To deal damage.
Genius.
But then again, duplicating the babies is kind of like a lot of damage.
Which is kind of crazy, and with the, you know, money equals power, it's essentially a double value out of money equals power.
So, you know, I'm just gonna go.
I think it's fine.
Sorry.
I'm okay.
One day at a time.
Oh!
Okay, we're fine.
I don't know why I just overreacted to that.
Like, what is that?
Treasure rooms become devil deals?
But there are no treasure rooms!
Boo!
Wait, is this a trinket?
Oh, I can't take it anyway, because I got a tick.
But that's a cool item, though.
I like it.
I'll definitely think about picking that up in the future.
I can't believe I did this.
One coin, that means we're not going to the shop.
What the...
Oh, they're shooting bombs.
That explains it.
Okay, we got to do this real quick before we lose the buffer.
This is an emergency.
We got to kill him fast.
Oh, he's the one that jumps!
I'm dead!
Well, I didn't mean I'm dead.
I meant I was going to lose my buffer, you know?
Safety pin.
This may actually not matter for me at all.
Shit!
It's not going to affect my babies.
Ouija board.
Yeah, tears are useless for me, isn't it?
Yeah, it's useless.
I'm not going to pick any of this up.
It kind of sucks not being able to shoot.
None of these stats affect you.
Oh, wait, let's not go in there.
Now, I could be totally wrong here and that, you know, the stats will actually affect me.
I just, I can't feel it.
My gut assumption here, my gut feeling is that it doesn't.
Based on that upgrade I got before.
Also, we picked up something.
Oh, right.
Okay.
I don't care about this.
We also have the devil, which is useless for me, I think.
Then again, damage could actually be useful.
I think that may actually scale my baby, one of the babies.
Not the red one, the other one.
Look how slow he is.
Oh, fuck.
Pill.
Nice.
Don't think that works on me though, but you know, whatever.
These guys are not slowed.
Okay, so we have one and a half black hearts.
Kind of makes me not want to go into the curse room.
So I'm not going to do it.
Yeah, fuck that.
I want to keep these.
These are very meaningful.
If they were blue hearts, then I wouldn't care.
Time to move on.
Yeah, and with one coin, we're not doing that room either.
Then again, is there anything I could do in there possibly?
No, not without any money, unfortunately.
It's kind of weird that there's no treasure rooms in the challenge runs.
Because you would think the challenge is all about the weird situation you're in with the character.
Wait, why did I go here?
Autopilot.
That's a lot of bombs.
That's totally worth two keys.
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, nothing.
I can just leave.
Hold on.
Six is...
Re-roll all items.
It's an idea.
I'm actually kind of intrigued by that.
Wait, does that mean?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if I re-roll and I lose my babies?
Then I can't shoot at all.
Absolutely not.
Imagine that.
Holy crap.
Yeah, that's not happening.
That's too risky.
Wow, he was tanky.
I cannot believe it.
Okay, this way.
What a weird room.
Also, I think I'm going to save money now.
Am I, though?
Probably not.
It's not that much damage you get, you know?
No, I'm going to find the boss first and then we're going to hit in there afterwards.
I need this buffer.
In fact, I wouldn't mind getting a couple more blue hearts before then.
Just so I can do some deals.
Fight room!
Not yet.
Get slowed.
Why am I shooting so slow?
I feel like I'm in slow motion right now.
I can't pick it up anyway because I got ticked.
Okay, here we go.
Oh god!
Dude, he's so fast!
You can't outrun him!
I literally could not outrun him!
Fucking hell, man!
And I get the worst item in the game for that?
That's bullshit.
Wow.
Crazy.
I think I'm a little upset at spaghetti now, guys.
That did it.
We're going to do fights closed?
Sure.
Everything's going bad now.
I have a good theory on where the secret room is.
I'll show you.
It's right here.
I don't even want to check the other walls.
Boom.
A pill!
I like pretty fly.
And now we leave.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
So the door opens when you have full red hearts.
That's what's happening.
Where's the thing?
I guess I'll just write it here.
No, wait, we have a fight room.
Opens when full red hearts?
It could also be opens when you don't have any buffers, you know?
I'm going to have to double check that next time.
It's definitely one or the other.
Okay, let's go.
Good shit.
It's mom time.
Of course, I lose my deal immediately.
That's crazy.
I don't know why I just turned into a seagull.
That's what happens when you play this game.
No!
Bro!
All this money is not going to make me happy if I die early.
Guys, it's over.
Holy crap.
You know what?
I'm going to duplicate.
I don't have faith in my skills.
I'm dead.
I did not see what I got hit by, like at all.
No clue.
Unlucky.
Unfortunate end to that.
That was such a good run as well.
Honestly, the only reason I...
I died in that run is because of that bullshit boss that I could not outrun.
Literally, did not have the speed to outrun.
I couldn't do anything.
Like, that's just... that felt terrible.
If that hadn't happened, I would have had my buffers.
I would have been fine.
Dude, four steps and nothing in that room, by the way.
Step room is not kind to me.
Okay, at least we got some healing here.
I need 10 rocks.
I got three bombs ready for your ass.
Yeah.
Dude, I should have had the converter.
I could have converted all my shit to red hearts.
And I could have been able to heal last run.
Yeah, why not?
It's exciting.
The moon!
Fuck yeah.
Are we going full pill?
Pill maxing?
I think we're going to kill at least a couple.
Alright.
Well...
Actually, one more.
Do one more.
Shit.
Okay.
No fear.
Whoo!
Masterfully navigated.
Fuck.
If I'd gotten hit by that bomb, I couldn't leave the room without dying, by the way.
I got one coin.
That is so sad.
I can't even... Dude, look at this.
Three dollars for that.
Oh wait, wait, wait.
Actually, blow this guy up.
Yike!
Also...
We're taking both.
Now I'm ready for the second floor.
Buffer in hand.
Babies in toe.
We got it.
Guys, there is actually a hundred percent chance that I will succeed with this challenge, this time around.
Because chances of getting that boss again that chases me that I cannot run is pretty much zero, so I can only win.
This is a guaranteed win.
There's no way I lose this.
Nice!
So the question is, which do I go for?
None of them, maybe.
Yeah, none of them yet.
Okay, look!
It's closed!
I do not have full red heart!
And I have a buffer!
So let's see what happens.
Actually, more buffers is good, too.
Wait, some of these babies are auto-aiming.
Oh,
God, I feel a sneeze coming!
I'm contorting my face.
I'm okay.
It's Steven.
We got tinted rocks!
Look at this combo here.
We're going to wait for him.
Hey, come to me!
Come to me!
Boom!
That's how you feed two birds with one scone.
Okay, check it out.
I'm going to use my...
Wait, how does this work?
Wait, shit, what does this do again?
Opens all closed doors in the current room.
Bypasses locks in most doors...
Oh!
I thought it was for the chest as well.
Oh, crap!
Oh, wait, what is this?
I have a... Remember... Remember is that it's bad.
Okay, three black hearts, though, yo.
Ah, for two red?
Absolutely not.
Go fuck yourself.
Not happening.
Never.
So now I'm wondering...
Are we like, forever locked out of angels?
Or can I like, regain some angel trust over a couple floors?
I'm actually going to experiment with that.
We're going to try and see if we can get the angels back.
Even though I did go in there.
Maybe it's impossible, maybe not.
I don't know.
I'm going to go in here.
Okay, that's...
Yeah, blow me up here!
That was the best suicidal bomb of all time.
Except this room is kind of bad.
A backpack.
Oh!
Mama mega!
Oh, God, I can't afford it.
Oh, I would love to afford that.
Imagine...
Shit.
That's so sad.
There's no way I'm getting that money.
Even with the...
Oh, let's check this now.
It's closed!
So maybe it is because I need to get rid of my buffer.
Yeah.
Also, I have no bomb, so I can't even get these chests.
Crap.
Can I even get in there?
No, I can't.
Damn it.
Alright, I guess we're leaving.
Get out of here.
Would you look at that?
I guess tears don't matter.
But the buffer does.
No, not the last.
I absolutely hate it.
Worst curse in the game.
Change my mind.
We're going left around.
I'm left maxing now.
Guys, I think I just realized how I could have survived the boss that chased me.
No, not the boss, but the bomb that chased me.
Instead of running from the bomb, you run and shoot the bomb.
That's all.
Thank you for coming to my TED Talk.
Okay, left max.
No, no.
Actually, we're cooking here.
Wait, why was this door open?
What?
Shit makes no sense.
I have no idea.
Why did that just open?
I have full red hearts and buffer just like I had before.
Crap!
Hey, how did that hit him?
Let me grab this.
Oh, is that AWAS?
AWAS me.
Okay, ants.
Oh, it's useless for me.
At least on this floor.
We're still left maxing.
Dude, if you left max, you gotta go all the way.
Yeah!
We're being rewarded.
Good shit.
I could do that.
No, I can't.
I need bombs.
Why am I so small?
It's the binky.
Okay.
I'm a baby.
I'm becoming a baby just like my babies.
Destroyed poop, spawn a blue attack, fly.
Yeah, because I think the current one I have is useless because it doesn't affect my tears.
Because it's my baby's tears.
Stick to the left.
Dude, this is exactly like Yulith.
How is this not any different?
Or how is this any different?
This way now?
I'm actually kind of proud of my dodging there.
That was a rare, really good dodge.
It was calculated.
It wasn't random.
Left maxing is this way.
Yes!
Bring it on, mega fatty.
I'm gonna show you who's daddy.
Easy.
Nailed that.
That's useless for me.
Angels, it does work!
I've gained good faith with the angels.
Active contrition.
Hold on, I need to Google this real quick on my something.
I don't have a phone nearby.
Fuck!
Plus one eternal heart allows angel rooms to appear even if a devil deal has been taken.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Okay!
So it's if you take a devil deal.
Oh!
Shit!
Okay, so for now I can always peek.
But not speak.
I love it.
It's good.
Good stuff.
I also have one bomb with me.
I will not spend it in here.
No, sir.
I will save it.
I could go... No, no, no, I can't.
This way.
Also gotta remember to use the key on doors.
Oh, shit.
Wow, the damage was crazy there.
These things have a lot of HP and I one shot that thing.
Oh, man.
I should have used my active.
Whoops.
Also, I got 22 coins.
Surely I can do something with that.
We don't know what that is.
What is that one again?
Restock.
Yeah.
I like that.
That means I can take multiple blue hearts now if I want to.
And a bomb.
Oh, I don't have a map.
Guess I'll take this.
Oh, I don't have any money anyway.
Shit.
I'm gonna save my bomb.
It's too valuable.
I think I've solved all my issues when I have curse of lost guys.
It's actually just left or right maxing.
That's how you solve that.
And now we've done it.
That was that.
The whole map has been cleared now.
Eternal heart, wonderful.
Okay, so wait, this door is... Ah, wait a sec!
There are different versions of this, right?
There's a normal fight club and there's a fight club plus plus.
This is fight club plus plus.
Maybe I need a black card to get in here or something.
If we're thinking in terms of hearts now.
Ansys!
Okay,
uh, do I use my one bomb?
Yes.
This is a big floor.
Hate these inanimate objects.
They're gonna be the end of me.
Fuck!
Stay at max range.
Yeah, good.
Oh my god, I almost got hit.
These rooms are no joke.
Ah, I could do it, but I'm not going to.
I have made the decision.
Nice!
That's so huge.
I need my bombs.
That means we can get into the secret room up there.
I feel
like dad's key is kind of bad.
Wait!
Wait a minute!
Can I use dad's key on the door to fight room?
Never mind, dad's key is good.
More I love that.
Anyway, I was about to say, I think dad's key is kind of bad, because you end up with so many keys, usually anyway, that you don't really need it to open doors.
You know what I mean?
If it also opened chests, then it would be kind of good, you know?
But now that it also... Oh my god, stop running into those fucking things.
What am I being hit by?
Insanity.
Hardest room in the game.
Thank you dad's key.
Actually, worst item now.
It made me want to go in there, and it was a bad idea, so thanks.
I now hate the item.
Keys galore.
You heard it?
Meow.
Off to the side.
Blast it!
Oh man, what a shitty room.
Should never have come here.
Okay, we got to do the boss on half a buffer.
Wish me luck.
It's the fallen.
Wow, that was fast.
Oh crap.
Oh, you've got to be fucking with me.
The mark.
Speed, damage, black.
Yeah, I guess that's fine.
We still have secret rooms to find.
We're not done.
Guys, I suck at this game.
That's key.
There's no bigger disappointment in binding of Isaac than when you go into the shop and you see this asshole standing here instead of actual items.
Every time, I cry.
I'm not a worst feeling in the entire game.
Also, where am I tinted rocks at?
You want bombs?
I'll give you some bombs.
Yeah, fuck the key.
I don't like the key.
Wait, if I... Oh wait, I shoot it.
I can do this now.
Sick.
I do like that.
I think you can make some crazy plays with the TNT.
The detonator.
The resonator.
I think there's maybe a... No, we found all secrets.
Moving on.
A little turd came out.
Hit the right guy.
Oh no, I hate stones.
How will I survive this?
Dude.
There we go.
Oh yeah, line him up.
That was so satisfying.
Mental health restored.
27 coins.
I better find a shop that works or I will be supremely unhappy.
Okay, we got a buffer.
We need to take advantage of this.
Adversary.
No, no.
This is for you.
Tick.
Okay, no more bombs.
Kill him.
What?
Okay, we got him.
Nice.
No, not this.
This is the worst.
I hate this item so much.
Ooh.
Okay, that's good though.
Two of diamonds.
These are clubs, transform, all pickups, chests, trinkets, and enemies.
Let me think.
Oh, so wait, pickups.
Pickups, chests, trinkets, and enemies.
I'm guessing these are pick up able bombs.
I'd rather have this.
Wait, wait, hold on.
We got to do a quick test here.
Field test.
Okay, lands there.
Nope.
Range does not affect this, unfortunately.
Oh, wait, it's not on a timer.
Right.
Oh God.
I think I got a bomb some stuff here.
Really?
Let me take this.
Actually, wait, wait.
We keep this card?
No.
Take this, and then we... Yeah, yeah.
Here's the plan.
We're just gonna go back first, explore fully, and then when we're done with that, we come back here and switch out this card if we haven't used it for the other card.
No!
I was doing so well.
Okay, okay, uh, no!
I thought all of them would get turned!
What is this shop?
I take it back, guys.
There's actually something worse than finding the asshole inside the shop.
It's this shop right here.
This is atrocious.
Like, what even is that?
Why is there only one item in there?
Wait, temperance?
Oh, right.
Maybe I'll do it.
Now I have 52 points.
Shit!
Do not take damage.
Oh, no, I don't trust this.
Whoo-hoo!
Close one.
I should have used the the bomb card in here.
Worms.
No.
A wall of babies.
Are the doors open?
Even more money.
Good.
Okay, I mean, I'm getting some good items here.
We have two buffers now as well.
It's not the worst.
Could go into the curse.
I'm doing it.
Could be life-changing.
Shit!
It ain't life-changing.
But I didn't lose anything on it, so.
It's okay.
I think I'm done on this floor.
Move on.
That one.
We're gonna have maximum angel now, I think.
So, wait, is mom here or not?
I'm actually not sure.
The boss says it's at the end, but I'm not quite sure.
Let me see.
Wonderful!
Holy water.
That's good.
Nice.
What's that?
Strength.
Very good.
Oh!
Whoo!
Hell, yeah.
Thanks, buddy!
Now, go to hell.
Easy.
Okay, well, I got a key now as well.
I don't know if I can use that.
Probably not.
Oh, god!
I mean, I'm swimming in bombs now.
This is fantastic.
And with the boom, you know.
Good comp.
Okay, so, wait, wait, wait.
Why is the door closed?
I think it's because I need black hearts.
That is my guess on why that... or, oh, or, I need to not have full red hearts.
Maybe it's the inverse.
Maybe I need to take red heart damage to get in there.
You know, one of them requires full hearts, the other one requires not full hearts.
Wanna jump?
Oh!
Whoa!
That was kind of scary.
Get petrified!
Step into my office.
73 coins, man.
I think a shop is due.
A shop with a... with a refresh machine.
You know, I need to be able to spend my money on something here.
It is essential.
Where are you?
There we go.
Let's do this one.
Or I can spend my money in the arcade!
This guy's just gonna give me battery, no?
Oh, no, this is the worst arcade of all time!
What the hell is that?
Man.
That's unreal.
Guys?
Why?
Oh, wait.
What?
Oh, it's because of the lighting.
Look at the rocks in the bottom left.
It looked like it was tinted.
But there's no X on it, but it was tinted.
So it confused me a little bit.
It was just the lighting.
Hey!
No, I stepped at the thing!
I did it twice.
Like, completely and utterly useless.
So I think this is Mom.
I'm actually scared of going in.
I can't do it yet.
You like my office?
I just had it remodeled.
Sure, give me more.
Come on.
Yes!
We got items to buy.
Mom's box.
Let's see.
Sponsored trinket.
It's gonna take us to 3 out of 3 on Yes Mother, but that's useless, essentially.
So whatever.
Clearing room spawns 2 rewards instead of 1.
Wait.
Yeah, okay.
Oh!
I got the refresh!
Yo.
This is gonna be sick!
No, I'm getting shitty items.
No, no, no!
Yeah.
Oh, I'm poor now.
I'm poor now.
That was that.
That was fun.
I may actually take this box.
I think this is the one I like the most.
Pushpin.
Chance to fire tears that are piercing in spectral.
But does that even work with me though?
Wait, let me check.
Can I check my spectralness somewhere?
Maybe in here.
Let's see.
Chance to fire them, huh?
I've got five lock.
I think we can safely say it doesn't do shit.
Use the trinket.
But let me think.
This one was what?
Two link tunnel openings which allow Isaac to teleport between them.
I mean, it's good for entering a curse room, I guess.
That isn't actually not a bad idea.
Consumes a key to launch sharpened keys.
Enemies killed by the key have a chance to drop pickups or a pedestal item reward.
That is actually also kind of sick.
I mean, we have a bunch of keys, right?
I think I'm gonna start by getting this one.
We're gonna go to the curse room now.
And use this on the curse room.
Oh wait, can I even get that?
Oh!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, I thought that was an active!
That's amazing!
Okay, that item just jumped up in quality for me.
I thought it was like a shit item, but the fact that it's a passive?
Wow!
That's crazy.
I'm not gonna step in here.
I'm just taking in some money.
Let's go straight to curse room, actually.
So,
I mean, that's pretty cool.
So this one is still close, unfortunately.
I don't want to experiment by going below max health right now, just to test that.
We're gonna have ample opportunity for that later.
Wait, where did those two hearts go?
Something just happened.
Oh, right!
Okay, so when I pick one up, the other gets... I see.
I get it.
I see.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go grab the key thingy.
I'm done with the razor.
Actually, wait.
No, I'm gonna keep using this until I get a good trinket.
Yeah, I would rather do that.
Do we have battery?
There's actually a battery.
Oh, okay, okay, hold on, hold on.
Door stop.
Wait, boss rush exit.
Boss rush exit remains open.
Huh?
Okay, hold on.
Cartridge.
10% chance to trigger the game kit effect when taking... no.
I mean, this one's useless for me anyway, so I'm gonna try this.
Mom!
What is Mom?
Get petrified!
Dude, the damage is crazy!
Wow!
That was a good amount of damage.
In fact, I'm gonna petrify her when she comes down again.
Come on, Mom!
There we go.
I'm gonna grab that.
Polaroid?
Angel?
Oh, we robbed the Angel already.
Shit.
Okay, guess we're moving on.
I told you there was a hundred percent chance we're gonna win.
See?
Look, this is the normal one.
It's open because we have max red hearts.
Oh, what a throw.
We spawned some kind of skull.
That was kind of crazy.
Yo, this room is crazy.
Okay, we did it.
Let me see what this is.
Cursed skull.
When damage to half a heart remaining, Icy instantly teleports to...
Oh,
I guess it is a way to get out of jail free, but you get teleported to a random place that may not be nice, you know?
Oh, fuck!
Man, that's always gonna fuck me up.
Because I always think, oh, I can just take everything that's there.
It is so unnatural for me.
Okay, so I can choose now.
So I open the chest.
Yeah.
Chance to fire a slowing shot.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't work for me.
Heels for red hearts whenever Icy unlocks something?
No.
Dude, I just thought of the craziest combo.
Imagine?
Imagine.
You have backpack, right?
You have backpack, and you have this box, and you have a smelter.
Oh, now we're talking, right?
That's a crazy combo.
Shit!
Actually, I didn't need that heart anyway.
Okay, so I can choose now.
I want coin.
Chest.
Gun to beam.
Also pretty useless, man.
All these trinkets have sucked so far.
Terrible.
There's no shops down there anyway, so.
Let me as well gamble.
Don't take that.
Oh yeah, we can step across little chasms here.
I can take both.
That's actually super huge.
Oh my god, please.
If I lose this eternal heart, I am going to cry.
Wait, why did the thing not hit him?
The holy water had no effect.
I feel cheated by the holy water.
Vibrant bulb.
Safety scissors.
Diffuses troll bombs and conversements bomb pickups.
No, no, no, no.
This one increases all stats when active health items are full.
I guess it's better than what I have.
I don't know about this boss rush thing.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, very beautiful.
That's a guaranteed one now.
That was a beautiful dodge.
Oh my god.
Wait, one.
What's one?
Oh, oh, uh, guys, I'm actually tempted to do it.
I mean, okay, wait, we're not doing terribly bad.
Like, this is fine.
Maybe I'll come back.
I may come back for this.
I need to think on it.
Here's the boss.
Uh, trinket, butt penny.
No.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Uh,
no, go.
Wait, is, is this not the last boss or?
Holy shit, man.
He got roped at.
He stepped into my office and realized it was a bad decision.
This is gonna be useless for me, so we take this one.
We're pill-maxing.
Retro-vision.
Okay.
Yeah, you gotta be kidding me, right?
This door better be open.
You know what?
Fuck it.
I feel good.
Take me home.
We got a bunch of HP somehow.
I don't understand what happened, but I love it.
There's a healing back here as well.
That was totally a protest.
Uh, re-roll there.
Okay, let me actually see what we got.
Uh, BFFs.
Oh, at least it didn't re-roll these.
That's good.
Dessert.
Dinner.
Wait, can I shoot?
No, but I have a shield now.
Ooh, sick.
Loadstone.
Here's the magnetize.
Abbot ladder.
Okay.
All right.
Gubby's collar.
Placenta.
Very nice.
Mom's purse.
Two trinkets at the same time?
That's huge for me.
I've got trinkets everywhere.
Like this one.
And, and there's more and more somewhere.
There's actually a bunch.
One damage to hover it hard.
No, I don't like that one.
Maybe I'll take this one.
No, doesn't work for me.
This one.
Absolutely.
So wait, is my, uh, bulb active right now?
Why is my energy so low on my axe?
Whatever.
I'm going.
Oh my God.
Yeah, the healing.
We're totally red heart maxing now.
So that means we can go step.
If we find a stepper.
I'm definitely missing Steven's DPS here.
But other than that, it's not too bad.
The biggest part or biggest deal is that I got a bunch of HP.
This is actually probably a run saving.
It saved the run.
Wait, what?
I don't know what's happening.
Once again, a fake shop, which makes me sad.
No, wait, this is not a shop.
This is a chest room or something.
Pills.
Oh, fuck.
That's bad.
Blow everyone up in anger.
Placenta, come save me.
Look at this joker.
Open.
Oh man.
Ooh, uh, check this out.
And now we donate.
Awas!
Oh wait.
I could have stepped.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
Nevermind.
Let me have my victory.
It was cool.
Okay.
It looked cool.
Where's my Awas situation?
What the fuck was that?
It's nice.
Okay.
Holy crap.
Teleport to treasure room.
There's a planetarium.
Teleport it instead.
It's probably not though, right?
Also, where the hell are the floor decoracionas?
This one.
Yeah.
I don't know what that is.
Hot bombs.
Bombs, place bombs, deal contact damage.
Bombs, explosion, leave behind fires.
They can damage enemies.
That's immunity to damage from stationary fires.
Okay.
I like the effect it has on me visually.
Looks nice.
Uh, there's also a card back here.
Okay.
Well.
Whatever.
Give me this one back.
Keep donating.
Insanity.
Probably gonna lose that one though, unless we get another one.
Breakfast!
Nice.
We need any healing we can get right now.
Oh god.
Oh.
Nearly lost it.
This room sucks.
I don't want to be in there.
That is lovely.
My eternal heart is protected.
Oh.
It's not protected anymore.
There is no way I do this without taking damage.
Maybe.
I surprise myself.
Uh, oh wait, I can just step across.
Oh, hell yeah, dude.
Hell yeah.
Yeah!
Uh, actually, I'm happy that I lost the eternal heart.
Because I want buffers at the end here.
I want to be able to get, like, black hearts, you know?
This was actually good.
Manny has a lot of HP.
Come on, step in here.
Unfortunately, I don't have an office anymore.
This is the only unfortunate thing about the re-roll.
What the?
Man, man, man.
Definitely doing this.
A goppy's tail.
Increase the chance of chests.
Yeah, whatever.
One room left.
Wow.
What a boring room.
Here we go.
Wish me luck.
I'm gonna blow this gap.
Crap.
It lives.
I'm gonna use my strength.
Okay.
Now we just do damage.
I think we got this one in the bag, boys.
Uh, I don't like that he's spawning these guys, though.
Wait, whoa, what is that?
That's new.
Yeah.
Wait, we're not done?
Shit.
I thought that was it.
That's fine, though.
I'm gonna go smack Isaac.
No problem.
He's easy.
It's these rooms I'm more worried about.
Pro dodging, pro dodging.
Yeah!
How does he do it?
Man, fuck these objects.
Oh, my.
Whatever.
No.
Uh, right maxing.
Yeah, like, how do you dodge that?
Answer, you don't.
Uh, wait, I said right maxing.
I gotta follow the rule.
I've never seen this guy before.
This is new.
Flaming bones.
No, no, no, no.
Keep this.
Wait, what?
No, keep this.
Good.
Okay.
Placenta is doing work.
Oh, no, another one of these big guys.
Wait, I don't take damage from these fires on the floor.
I'm immune.
Well, they do block my path.
Teleports to the shop, but there's no shop, right?
Is there?
No, there's not.
Nothing to spend all my money on.
Well, now my right maxing build is kind of ruined.
What's that?
More bombs!
Now they also poison.
And I'm immune to poison.
I like.
Actually, you want to bait that shot out and then attack him.
Also, there's a tinted rock there.
I've got this guy's number now.
Now we bait.
Okay, he died.
Okay, then.
Callus.
That may... let me think.
No, that's not gonna matter for me.
I'd rather have the stats up.
Let's do you guys.
Run into my fire.
The Empress.
Damage.
Speed.
I think that's useless for me, honestly.
But I may as well take it.
Really?
I dare you to come into this fire.
I had a little barricade set up there.
Oh, look at this.
Oh, boss is here.
Guys, we go for it.
I need to see something real quick, though.
Notched axe.
I don't want to swing it.
No.
Keep it at max, so we get the bonus.
Isaac!
You're gonna die.
It's gonna be so easy.
Wait, he's modified.
He's not normal.
It's a different Isaac.
Wait, what?
Oh, I used my thing.
Oh, no.
Unequipped.
I'm not playing well.
Nice.
The bombs are good.
Easy mode.
Easy.
We got it.
Success.
I told you that was a 100% chance.
Epic fetus.
Unlock challenge 11.
Not bad.
I wonder if that was because I did this challenge or because I unlocked the fetus.
Oh, it's what about eight?
What about eight?
Oh, well, glass cannon.
That sounds fun.
I see how it is.
One HP, a lot of damage.
Whoa.
Oh, no way.
Oh, what?
And we have the book of denial as well.
No way.
So that's what epic fetus is or what?
Replaces tears with an unlimited use, heavy damage, missile strike.
We yield the pickaxe.
What?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Loki's horns chance to fight tears and all board cardinal directions at once.
So wait.
Ah, I see.
Cool.
But what do you mean by X?
I'm so confused.
Oh, airstrike.
That is awesome.
Oh, this is weird.
I dig it, though.
Well, since we're kind of a glass cannon, I think we should focus on survivability.
So getting that heart is going to be priority.
Nice.
Also, what is this one?
Oh, wait, that's the one that spawns all cards.
I may actually take that instead.
Ancient recall.
OK, so we got wait, justice.
Yeah, justice.
Totally worth so far.
Doubling keys, teleport to the starting.
No, I don't need to do that.
In fact, I'm going to leave these here for now in case we get more keys.
Yeah, that's the plan.
I wonder if this airstrike is going to.
Whoa.
OK, this is going to be easy, guys.
Are you kidding me?
Easiest challenge of my life.
There is no way I lose this.
The chariot is nice, actually.
Chance will destroy poops.
Yeah, why not?
So the thing that's coming down is actually a fetus.
That's kind of messed up.
And we do this now.
Wow.
Jesus.
Sure.
Justice.
Oh, nice.
I like that one.
Justice.
Unfortunately, not the right heart.
Six gold.
I can buy another blue heart.
I'm going to do it.
We're going to say fuck you to the curse room.
Oh, let's double the keys to this one.
I don't need I don't need this one.
No, I don't need the food.
Good.
Solid.
Actually, should we blow this guy up?
I guess bombs are useless for me.
Like, what would I even use those for?
I got to do it.
What if I find something, something, you know?
I'm totally min maxing and I like it.
Oh, actually, wait, wait.
Does it work on walls?
If not, I can use my bombs.
I'm going to try everything.
Amazing.
Okay.
I mean, this is just a guaranteed win.
There is no way in hell I can lose this game.
Show me the other room.
Maybe it's in here.
I can't wait.
I have chariots.
I could go in.
Uh, but I, I'm going to lose HP on going out.
But I feel like my HP is so important that I'm not actually going to do it.
I value it too much.
This one we checked already.
Let's just move on.
Every bit of HP matters right now.
Ah, here we go.
Ah, what?
Let's... moving on.
I wish the chariot would stay active after entering the room for like the duration that it's active, you know?
So I can quickly enter, check what's going on, and then out again.
Okay, so check it out.
This door is still closed.
Uh, I don't have a black heart and I also have one red heart.
So maybe...
I mean, I think we're still on track to test the theories.
I wonder though if I can take damage from my own fetuses.
Okay, now we need a shop.
This is actually an amazing challenge.
I'm having so much fun with this one.
Puberty!
I gotta check it all.
Oh god.
Nice, we needed that.
Uh oh.
Uh, small rock is the damage.
Okay.
Why is it following me?
Ding dong.
Get owned.
Oh, that's huge.
Bandage, baby.
Love it.
And we're gonna find stuff in poops as well.
Guys, we're going angel.
Like, no matter what.
We're not done on this floor.
We gotta find secrets too.
Nice.
Oh, I love to see this.
It's pill time.
Question.
Will the liberty work on my bombs here?
Does it have randomized effects?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I don't think so.
I can see for it.
Okay.
Not bad.
Also, I'm mega rich.
Ultra mega rich.
Which is awesome.
Mystery gift.
Guys, I'm gonna use this in the room with the boss so I can get more HP.
This is the big thing.
Now you may say, what about the devil room?
I'm gonna give a fuck about that.
Wait, do I?
Hold on.
It's for free, right?
Give the consumer spawn a random pedestal item from the chances.
That's for free.
Contract from below decreases the likelihood of a room clear reward.
Okay, but the doubles the room clear reward.
Also, now that I'm in here.
Oh, guys.
Guys.
Oh, but it takes both my red hearts.
Oh, it is a big decision.
Wow.
Hold on.
Let me destroy these.
I need to see if there's like a blue heart here.
If I... Okay, this is... Guys, we're gonna embrace the challenge.
The glass cannon challenge.
This is the ultimate glass cannon.
Boom!
We're doing it.
I believe.
Trust.
It's gonna be great.
Then we have shop here.
We buy this, of course.
We can also re-roll.
Oh!
Aha!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's awesome.
Oh my god.
Wait, what's this?
Where's the layout?
I don't care about that.
Pokego could be cool, I guess.
No.
I'm gonna re-roll.
Pill and... Wait, where's that one?
Oh, there's one.
What's that one?
Diplopia duplicates all pickups and item pedestals.
Yes.
Wait, that counts!
Oh, wait, Bookworm is not gonna do anything to me, I guess.
That is funny.
Okay, so if I do this now, it still doesn't have Book of Blyll.
Wait, coupon!
Uh... So wait, if I re-roll now, are all the pedals still gonna be affected?
Oh, come on.
No, not all of them.
Okay, some of them.
Actually, almost none of them.
What the hell?
No, wait, we got starter deck?
Can hold two cards now.
Uh, all future pill drops are replaced.
Actually, yeah, I'll take that.
The Fool?
We also have this pill.
I'm definitely eating that.
Okay, um, get the key.
What's this one?
Oh, the Fool.
Wait, that's the third one?
No, it's the same.
The question is, uh, coupon though.
If I coupon and...
No, I think I'm gonna stick to the Satanic Bible.
I'm gonna pick this up.
Do that again.
And now we're gonna go up here and blow this up now.
Okay, let's re-roll and we get money!
Um, what about this guy?
More!
No, I didn't mean to buy it!
Crap!
Fuck.
Whatever.
Shit.
It's okay.
Uh, I'll be back.
Uh, no, no, thank you.
That sounds horrible.
I'm almost positive that I take damage from this, uh, fetus.
Oh my... Dude, I shouldn't have destroyed the re-roll thingy!
God, I thought for sure there's no way I'm gonna get money again.
But here we are!
It's insane.
I can still buy the bag, I guess.
I'm still a little baggy I can get.
Would love to get some kind of item now that gives me more, um, charge.
Oh my god.
What happened there?
At least we confirmed that we take damage from the drop down.
No, no, no.
Stop picking it up!
Yeah, okay.
I... Wait!
So I don't have any red hearts, but I also have black hearts.
I'm at a complete loss for this door.
Maybe it's not based on the hearts at all, this one.
The other one is for sure, not that one though.
Yeah.
Okay, uh, so we can hold two cards at once.
I may actually go back and take the fool.
Also, I'm really slow.
I need to find some speed.
This just won't do.
And buy this one.
Do I get a key?
I... This battery...
Yeah, it's worth.
Uh, you know what the smart thing would have done would be?
I should have taken this satanic bible, recharged that, and then switched it out again.
But, you know, too late.
Let's
go.
Amazing floor.
I can't lose.
I'm willing to bet like everything.
I'm not gonna lose.
I will give away my channel to one of you guys if I lose this.
And it's up to you to carry on the torch after this.
I didn't mean to blow this up but that's okay.
Wait, so we go here and then down.
This one took me a while to figure out.
But now I got it.
Strength and more strength.
I'll take one strength.
What's the other one?
Chariot, okay.
This may be one of the few times where a mouse could be good here.
I turned off the mouse though because it was annoying to see the cursor at times, you know.
How come there's like a double?
Oh, no way.
Okay, okay.
So the... what's it called?
Bookworm does work on this.
That's what's happening.
It's shooting two at a time sometimes.
Reroll!
Amazing.
Okay.
What do we want?
Load this up.
Money me.
Oh, that's risky.
Bogo bombs.
All bomb pickups become double bombs?
No, thanks.
Jar of Flies.
No.
These suck ass, so we're not taking them.
The battery is intriguing.
I'll be back when I find more money.
I'll do this one.
Sure.
And with the poop we have, we're actually gonna find a lot of money.
Assuming we find poops.
Duct tape.
No.
Okay, almost full on mana.
You know what?
Let's do this one now.
It's too...
Wow.
Damage is very good, guys.
Yeah.
Absolutely delightful.
If we find a donation machine, I have something very, very cool that I want to test.
Let's see if we find one.
Also 20 monies, by the way.
Wait, the fool.
That can be used, actually.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, actually, no, we can't do this.
That's a bad idea.
Absolutely bad idea.
Okay, I'm gonna go in here and use fool.
Wait, was this the starting room?
I guess it was.
Check it out, check it out.
500 IQ.
Actually, a little more.
Super magnet, I don't need that.
The tower, I don't need that either.
More money, great.
For the roll.
Yikes.
Whoa, it's open, it's open.
Then I enter.
Wonderful.
What a shot that was.
And that was that.
That's all she wrote.
We even found both secret rooms.
Actually, amazing.
Let's go to the shop now.
I need to find speed.
That's my one really big disadvantage right now.
Here's the thing though, if I... check it out.
If I blow it up to re-roll instead, then I will maintain 30 coins, which means I can buy potential 215 coin items.
So it may actually be in my interest to blow it up instead of... Actually, we have one coin here though.
Wait, one try.
Damn, let's blow this guy up.
Nothing.
Let's do it.
No, oh wait, that's straight.
Oh, I thought it was the backpack.
Potato peeler.
Consumes a red heart container to grant a permanent cube of meat familiar and permanent damage up.
I mean, at this point, I don't even need my red heart.
I've got to be honest with you.
So maybe I'll just... No, no, wait, I do need my book though.
I can't be running around with notebook.
Yeah.
Well, now I kind of regret blowing up the machine.
Fuck.
I gambled.
It didn't pay off.
It happens.
The sun is not gonna be super good for me, but it's still decently good.
Let's leave.
Off we go.
I can't lose.
Okay, six seven percent chance to find demons.
Oh, I'm so blacked out right now.
No spikes.
Like, this is not even a challenge.
This is just a joyride.
That's what this is.
I'm not gonna enter that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
I played bad.
The explosion radius is getting bigger, it feels like.
Oh my god.
Oh, I got him.
Haha.
He was servicing right on top of me.
It was tactical.
I knew he was gonna be there.
That's why I did it.
Easy.
It's like playing a pool.
You know, you're splitting the triangle or whatever.
Gotta find a shop.
So wait, wait, wait, can we enter down here?
No, we can't.
Why not?
What is the condition for that one, man?
Losing my damn mind.
Also, we gotta look for secrets.
More money.
51 coins.
There's the shop.
Oh, I stepped into a thingy.
Endless nameless?
Chance to spawn a copy of a card pillow rune that was used.
Yeah, actually, that sounds... No!
I'm so sad.
I cry every time.
And more money just to rub it in.
Feels bad, yo.
Okay, let's just keep moving.
Next floor, we're gonna spend the money.
Trust.
It's gonna be good.
So many red hearts are spawning, man.
If I wasn't, you know, glued and blacked up right now, I totally would go stepping.
Mega man.
Wait, I'm Judas?
It's a Judas?
Goat head.
Devil deals?
I'm actually gonna say no to that because I want angels.
And if I take this, I'm gonna have to sacrifice blue and black hearts and I can very easily find myself in a situation where I don't have any HP.
So I'm actually gonna reject this.
I say no to that.
Only smart plays here today.
I think we're done.
No, wait, we have so much money.
Let's go to the arcade.
Now's the perfect opportunity.
Oh, can I also give this guy some money?
Bumble!
Wanders around consuming coin pickups from the ground.
Levels up as it consumes, gaining new abilities that can damage.
I like it, actually.
I'm not in need of that much money anymore, so it's cool.
Oh, this one!
Oh!
Lasting cap?
No, thanks.
Follow the dog.
I feel like that's somehow important in this game.
Two of hearts.
Uh, no.
Familius orbit around Isaac.
That may... No, no, no.
I don't even know what I would want here.
Okay, check it out!
So now I've lost some red hearts.
Let's, let's see.
I'm gonna go to this room down here.
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
At least we crossed that one off the list.
Oh, wait, we're consuming black hearts now.
Let's not do that.
Dude, this is crazy.
Infinite money glitch?
Oh!
Six, seven!
Eat it, eat it!
We're gonna make the little guy fat.
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Uh, I need to go get hearts.
There's hearts everywhere.
This guy's gonna be consuming all the hearts.
We're gonna make him fat.
We're gonna fatten him up for Christmas, and then we're gonna eat him.
Take him, take him.
Yeah, look at him!
Oh, no, I consumed the wrong one.
Whoops.
Not bad.
Oh, that's mine.
No, actually, you can, you can have that.
I wonder if they actually count for more, like he eats more.
Oh, look at him!
How many times does it happen?
It doesn't say.
Okay, let's just keep doing it then.
Wait, I spawned a blue heart?
Hey, at least he's consuming.
Uh, blow this up too.
Crap, crap.
Uh, well, sheisa.
Well, the thing is, we have a lot of money now, so the next shop is gonna be wild.
I'm happy with that.
Let's uh, let's uh, let's uh, take this blue heart here.
And leave.
Let's get the hell out of here.
This was a solid floor.
Real nice.
Actually, wait, wait, we haven't found all the secrets.
We gotta keep looking.
It could be in here.
The devil?
Uh, the star.
Oh, stars.
Hold on, do I have the thing that increases, look at this, increases chance of planetariums.
That's exciting.
I think we could maybe do something with that.
I'm gonna take it.
In fact, I have a genius play.
Are you ready?
Look at this.
Not bad, huh?
For an old timer like me.
Now there's this one, though, that's bothering me.
Where is the secret?
Not here.
Maybe, did I check this?
Uh, if I don't find it on the way up, I'm just gonna keep going.
Oh, what am I doing?
Someone's already checked.
Ah, maybe in here.
My god.
That's amazing.
Oh, oh, oh, this is a good one.
Guys.
Oh my goodness.
Steam six.
Uh, wait, wait, Mr. Me.
Member card.
I like that one.
But hold on.
If I take that, it means I can't take the others.
So I need to choose carefully here.
Uh, no re-roll, it seems.
No re-roll, okay.
Steam sale, I don't care.
I have enough money.
Mr. Me is exciting, but I have enough money, so this one, obviously.
Oh, they've become... Okay, I see.
Uh, then maybe I do take this.
That's three blue hearts, though.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
My active is already fantastic.
I don't need to change that.
I think I'll take this.
I think it's good.
We're gonna have close to 99.
Oh wait, this guy needed to pick up coins, right?
Okay, let's not move on yet.
Okay,
we're done.
Keep moving.
That was fantastic.
Uh, let's check this one real quick.
Oh my god, thank god I did.
Hey, coins!
Okay, okay, I got you.
Give me like a breakfast, and I will love you a long time.
The black bean.
When taking damage, Isaac releases several farts.
Oh, it's not a trinket!
Fantastic.
In that case, love it.
I am utterly rich right now.
No, that's horrible.
We want angels.
We're going angel style.
Okay, this one's open.
I guess because we don't have any red hearts, so there's no chance to have taken any damage on my red hearts.
It's still consistent.
Oh my god, oh my god, stop.
What the?
What did I just take damage from?
I don't know what happened.
Buffers!
Also, I think I'm gonna use the stars now.
Aw, man.
Too bad.
Another chariot.
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
Terrible.
Blue fires are my best friend with this build.
Man, the radius is so big on that explosion now that there's a high chance I damaged myself.
Uh, I think we just go for it here.
Gish!
Oh, man.
How are you hitting me?
Not playing so well right now.
Little gish, no thanks.
Wait, where's my angel?
Fuck it.
I can peek anyway, right?
Okay, let's have a see here.
Dark matter, chance was here.
No, that's horrible.
Uh, horrible.
Actually, the fear is good.
The fear is actually good, but it's not worth three blue hearts, I don't think.
What?
That's actually insane.
Uh, damn.
Damn.
I can't... Like, where are my angels at?
I need angels.
I need breakfast.
Or a big, big old sausage.
Would also do the trick.
He came back!
Unreal.
Wow.
Flight.
Chariots.
What is with these chariots?
Stop with the chariots, man.
Uh, I don't think this guy should be picking up any more coins.
Angelic spoils.
Defeated angels will drop angels.
If a key piece was previously collected, angels will spawn the other key piece before producing angel items.
Yeah, actually, let's keep that.
I will find angels, and we will fuck them up.
It will happen.
Uh, you know what?
Check this wall here.
Nice.
We gotta start building up the black hearts again.
Okay, dude.
Here we go.
Uh, battery, obviously.
This one.
What is that one?
I think it's the effect of the card held without consuming it.
I like it.
Reveal the world.
Take this back.
Let's check out what's down here.
Black heart and...
Wait, bombs didn't it?
I wonder if this works with my...
No,
it doesn't.
Okay.
I guess it's technically like a tier, you know?
It's not a bomb.
Oh, nice.
We're full on hearts now.
The full, no thanks.
Still 66 coins left.
Okay, dude.
Let's really try to understand this one.
We're gonna give it so much money now.
There's gotta be something here.
Oh!
No, wait, what?
I don't know.
This is, this room doesn't make any sense to me at all.
I don't get it.
The steel is heavier than feathers.
Actually destroyed this one, too.
There's sometimes items in there inside.
Lovers.
Two lovers?
Please be good.
Sadness.
How come the sun didn't reveal the other secret?
The hell's going on there?
Unless there isn't one.
I'm confused.
Uh, what about here?
I think I already tested this one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I don't know, man.
Maybe there isn't one.
Can I trust the sun at all?
Oh, I just want to check already.
The sun is lying!
Oh my god!
Okay, you can't trust the sun.
It's only going to reveal one of them.
Okay, you know what?
I think at this point I'll take this.
I have hearts to spare.
Yeah, I'm good.
Sweet.
Dank depths.
That was satisfying.
What do we have here?
Aha!
Nice.
Get that heart back up.
Perth Row.
That is a pretty good one.
Also, I don't think my familiar is gonna grow any more from coins.
We have reached maximum size.
Oh my god, what was that?
What the actual hell was that?
PhD!
Uh... yeah?
I mean, I'm rich.
Who cares?
Oh, it all pills and cards now.
The chariot returns again.
You know what?
I'm gonna use the sun here.
Reveal the map, whatever.
Give me the chariot.
And this one as well.
No, Scotland?
Interesting.
I wonder if that works.
Uh... okay, that's also good.
And in fact, I buy all.
And a rune.
Dagass.
What was that one again?
That's the one that gives me a...
Yeah, okay.
It was the cursed one.
Feels good to use my money, man.
This feels so good.
Oh yeah.
Best feeling ever.
I'll even buy that.
Because why not?
I thought I could hit both.
Unbelievable.
Even more money.
Jesus.
The moon, secret, but we're already here.
Okay.
Empress chariot.
Wait, which one do I want?
Gaining a bit of speed is actually not a bad thing.
Is it better than... yeah, it's better than chariot, I think.
I forgot I had Perth row.
I probably could have used that here somehow in a good way.
But whatever.
Could have probably used it there too.
But at this point, let's not get greedy.
You know?
I don't think this guy can grow anymore.
Robo baby!
Sick.
But
it's only when I do the homing missile thing.
Airstrike.
Chariots.
What's with the chariot, man?
I found 10 chariots.
Too many.
Destroy this too.
Wait, this one has a...
Guys, that one had an X on it!
And it dropped something.
You saw that?
It was briefly there.
Maybe you didn't see it, but I'm almost certain that had an X on it.
Let me destroy all these.
What the hell is that?
Fills every... oh!
Right, that one.
This is a big room we got here, so I think...
No, actually, there's a better room for this.
I have the craziest play in mind here, guys.
I'll show you.
This is going to be wild, okay?
It may actually be illegal.
I'm also going to destroy all these rocks, so I'm making maximum room here.
Okay, watch this.
I'm going to stand here.
Beautiful.
Now I go grab Perth row.
I think you can see where I'm going with this.
Oh, unfortunately, I don't have the poop anymore.
Or do I?
Somewhere.
Perth row.
Do I still have the poop master?
Damn, I think I left it behind.
That's too bad.
But there's probably some other good stuff in those poops.
It'll be fine.
Oh, this is going to take a while.
Or not.
No, he's going to pick up all the coins!
The little bastard!
We're racing against time.
Oh, wait, it doesn't... Oh, it doesn't duplicate coins.
Stop that.
This guy has a liability now.
I hate him.
Okay, that was a funny strategy, though.
We also have Degas now, which was the one that removes a curse and Grand Soul Arts.
Hopefully, I get cursed next floor, so I can get maximum satisfaction out of it.
Are we done here?
Almost.
I'm actually going to step.
Oh, no, wait, I thought it was a curse room.
This way.
What's happening?
Two of spades.
Hey, cool.
Now, I will never run out of keys.
Hope I find a key, dude.
That was bad.
Oh, my God.
Wait, was that answers?
You know what?
Yes.
We use it here.
Okay, so this is interesting.
The sun does not reveal the gray question mark, but answers does.
I wonder why.
This is good information.
Again, bruh,
I don't think I want the chariots.
Time for the boss.
Long time coming.
Is this a chariot again?
It is.
Dude, she's too fast.
What the fuck?
I'm having trouble controlling it when there's four of them.
The negative.
And go.
Solid.
Not bad.
I can't lose.
We are now inside her body.
Six, seven percent chance of angel.
I mean, demon.
What?
How did they hit me?
They died.
That didn't make any sense.
Wow.
Although I could.
Actually, I could.
Should I?
You know what?
I'm gonna.
I'm gonna do it.
Fuck yeah.
You can't stop me.
Conquest!
What was that sound you know?
Wow, he died fast.
Oh, I mean, this is good, but it's not that good.
So I have to replace my current.
My current is amazing.
We're gonna have to.
Oh, look at that.
Money equals power.
And Abaddon.
Speed damage.
Speed is fantastic here.
Replaces all heart containers with black hearts.
Plus two black hearts.
Chance of fire for your tears.
You know what, guys?
I actually like all of this.
I don't like that bomb, though.
This is not gonna add that much damage.
I like this one.
It's getting a little risky with the amount of HP I have, but I think it's fine.
Don't you dare.
Justice is good.
Nope, you're not taking that.
Oh, this is gonna be good.
Oh, there's a lot of them.
No problem.
Start working on the black hearts again.
Ooh, this guy wants coins, eh?
No, blow him up.
I saw him.
He was trying to be sneaky.
The tower is not great.
The moon is actually kind of cool.
This guy's picking up all my coins.
Imagine getting this guy in greed mode at the end.
That would suck so bad.
I mean,
I could just move on, but no.
We gotta get the energy and then get more black hearts.
Wow, that was nice.
Jira?
This one duplicates chests and pickups.
Cannot duplicate.
Okay.
Devil is not good for me.
Not bad.
What the fuck was that?
It's like a gravity field.
Oh, it's the guy in the center, I see.
Of course.
As soon as I hit full HP, I'm gonna move on.
Just... I like this one, actually.
The world.
Okay, the world...
Hold on a minute.
The world doesn't reveal the other secret room either.
So it's only answers.
The Empress.
That one is good as well.
I may actually grab it at some point.
Another world.
And we're done here.
So I got Jira and Daegis.
Actually, I think these are the best ones to hold on to right now.
Yeah, let's go.
Uh, let's blow a hole here.
I think we're done here.
I can still enter.
I mean, I've got 50 coins.
That's pushing it, man.
There's no guarantee we're gonna get a lot of hearts next floor, you know?
Like, it could go horribly wrong and then I'm gonna regret everything.
So let's not take that chance.
Yodero.
Oh, ah, here we go.
Daegis.
Remove the curse, baby.
Oh, that's so satisfying.
Very nice.
Thought they could curse me, huh?
I say no.
That was actually beautiful.
I'm not gonna be able to get that one, unfortunately.
Wow.
I'm getting better at dodging my own rockets.
Or fetuses.
Fidai.
I'm not sure what the plural is on that.
How did I not take damage from that?
Never mind, I did.
Damn.
It was almost flawless.
It was upon a secret.
Even more secrets.
Let's have a look.
How on earth am I gonna get this one?
Not that I want it, but the inner eye.
Less tears?
Hmm.
Does this work the way I think?
Okay, no, it doesn't.
But that's also cool.
Yeah, that's scary.
Sometimes it's four.
Because there's the extra one from Bookworm.
It's gonna be scary.
I mean, it's gonna be a lot of damage on one single target.
Which is nice.
Wait, question.
If I do this...
And then leave and come back.
I wonder if the bombs are still gonna fall when I come back.
We got more people in here?
Where's the...
Oh, it's down here.
Also, I don't think the boogers are working, unfortunately.
Enemies are just getting hammered.
Copy's color!
Uh, give me this.
So, there's no other effect with that, right?
Yeah, it's just...
Yeah, okay.
That's a nice reassurance, maybe.
I guess I don't even want anything from here.
Have cards, I guess.
That could have been a blue or black card, I guess.
Uh, you know what?
Fuck it.
Blow them all up.
Stop picking up my coins, badass!
Camouflage.
Oh my goodness.
Guys, it's not looking good.
I'm taking too much damage from my bombs!
No.
I don't like this.
Jesus fuck!
Oh, wow.
We gotta start working on those hearts.
Where's the boss?
There it is.
Just go.
Just do it, man.
Trust in me.
Holy crap!
Die fast!
Wait, we gotta...
We gotta go down?
Oh, no.
I'm not ready for that.
I was ready for Isaac.
I'm not ready for this.
Chill.
I can't walk on this!
I have to!
They cornered me!
Oh my god!
What is this one?
Mom's foot.
Guys, I think it's over.
I need some good luck with the blue flames.
Ah, man, it's over!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Doubles bombs?
Why not?
Doubles coins?
I've got a lot of items.
How am I taking damage?
For fuck's sake!
That's good.
I should have Jared that one.
Crap on a bicycle.
Get away from me.
Oh, wow.
Does a man really need more keys?
I mean, okay.
Okay, eat the coins, then.
Does it make you strong?
Why is he spawning bombs?
I hate this dude so much.
Look, he's spawning bombs again!
A school bag is actually kind of sick.
I want to banish this follower.
I hate it.
Oh, well, well, well.
Isn't that interesting?
That could be very good, actually.
What's that?
No, man, no.
Ah, reroll!
We're gonna reroll this.
Very close veins.
Launches a ring of 10 large tiers each time Isaac takes damage.
Are those tiers gonna be bombs?
He has to also briefly gain the...
That's too risky.
What if it spawns a bunch of fetuses from the sky?
I can't take that risk.
Oh, man.
This ain't good.
We can definitely get in here.
Spawn something good for me now, come on.
That's...
Can I get another Eternal Heart?
Please?
The Hank Man?
Okay, I like it.
Fuck you!
Also, how did those spiders not die just now?
What the fuck is going on?
Okay, whatever.
Move on.
Jesus Christ.
When I find two Black Hearts, I'm gonna Jira.
What the fuck is going on?
No!
It's over for me.
Pull yourself together.
Wait, I don't like High Priestess, give me this.
I saw that coming and I...
I need to find another Eternal Heart.
What was that one?
Cause it's tiers to...
Maybe a bad idea, I don't know.
Okay, I kind of want to do this.
Stars.
Please don't blow up in my face.
Of course, I step on it!
No.
No!
Oh my god, dude, it's over.
There's no way I can do this.
I can't do it.
I can't win.
Destroy this skull.
I need batteries.
I need to find secrets.
No, not the High Priestess.
Wait, the Empress?
Oh right, damage.
Hank, you know what?
Yes, I'm gonna become a flying man during that boss fight.
Cause I don't remember what the hell is going on, but let's just play it safe, you know?
I have no idea where this secret could be.
I'm not even gonna look for it, fuck it.
Wish me luck.
This is it.
It's a ton.
Oh my god.
We're not done yet.
Mommy!
Oh my god.
Fuck me, that was close.
That was so close.
I need a... we did it.
We did it.
Thank god I didn't have to give away my channel.
I just thought of that.
Man, that was close.
You know what I thought at the end?
If I just bomb enough, he's gonna die before I die.
Because there's a grace period when you take damage where you're like beeping, you know?
And you're immune to damage.
That was the plan.
Oh my god.
Way too many challenges, one with half a heart.
Yeah.
It's not luck though, it's skill.
It's skill.
What's up, Adusa?
What can I help you with?
This green is still... Dude, you're shaking.
I think you guys are, you know, coming together and trying to gaslight me or something.
I have no idea what you're talking about, man.
There's nothing going on.
I'm looking at it right now.
Guys, can you see any shaking?
Because I can't.
I don't see it.
I'm about to break 70,000 potatoes.
I don't have any idea how much that is.
Is that considered a lot around these parts or is that a little bit?
I don't know how much is a lot, you know?
100,000 potatoes is richness.
You have 160,000.
Okay, well, okay.
That's a lot.
You forgot about Eden the second.
I did actually not forget about it.
Because I wanted to do challenges.
We had to show the challenges some love.
Next time we're going to try out some new characters and also go green mode.
Maybe another challenge.
Because I'm actually really enjoying these challenges, especially that last one with the fetuses.
Yeah.
Don't litter on the streets.
Wait, what do you mean?
I'm not littering.
You're littering.
You're stuck in a hotel.
It was fun way to burn a couple hours.
I mean, aren't you always in a hotel, ghost?
You're always on the move, right?
One town to the next.
Or maybe you have more of a standard route you're taking.
So it's like the same hotels.
Nice.
It's streamlined now.
It's time for me to go eat some food and feed my cats.
And maybe play some Red Dead Redemption.
Yeah, probably.
Fetus fan.
I'm a fetus fan.
I'm also a Norman Reedus fan.
I want you to find tainted Isaac so bad.
I mean, I'm gonna find all of them in due time.
I hope.
We'll see.
Well, let me say this.
I'll find all of them as long as I'm still having fun finding them.
I mean, at some point I'm gonna get them, right?
Death Stranding, foreshadowing, maybe.
I've just been thinking about Death Stranding lately.
I'm looking forward to the second one so much.
It's gonna be a really special experience, I think, because I really, really loved the first one.
Jackie bit very cute.
Yeah.
Did you see that one?
It's on the...
If you haven't seen it yet, it's on my second channel.
I put up a video of Jackie.
I'm gonna put more Jackie videos, by the way.
I may film a video of her like every couple days or something and just put it up there, you know?
I gotta start monetizing my cat.
He's got a model for the internet.
I mean, I may as well do it, right?
People keep asking me for Jackie pictures or videos, so here we go.
Enjoy.
What's my least favorite character?
That's a good question.
Let me think.
Who do I hate?
I don't know, actually.
Because even Judas, I'm starting to like.
So I'm not sure.
Let me see here.
Jacob and Esau?
I haven't really tried it that much, but it was definitely weird.
Maybe my least favorite is...
I think either Eve or Lazarus.
Lazarus is just boring, in my opinion.
Magdalene is also a little boring.
Like, and even even the question mark guy, right?
The three question marks?
Even that guy is kind of entertaining because he's really unique compared to the others.
So yeah, probably Eve or Lazarus.
Those two.
Eve can be interesting if you get something going where you have less than half Red Heart or something, right?
The Blue Baby Enjoyer, yes.
I kind of want to try and unlock the second version of Blue Baby.
I wonder what that's going to be.
That's probably going to be crazy.
Imagine how difficult it's going to be as well to unlock that.
What happened to, no reason to play anyone but Esausel?
I mean, nothing happened to it.
Honestly, at this point I feel the same.
If it's all about winning, you would play Esausel every single time.
The character is just better than all the others.
It's that simple.
Hand me Esausel and I can make anything happen.
Do you have Silksong, Hollow Knight, OSTs?
I do, actually.
A couple.
One of my favorite ones are from Hollow Knight.
I forget the area you're in when it plays, but well, I don't want to spoil the name of the area, but it's like a very somber melody.
It's something I played a lot when I did Rainworld.
I used it as the map music.
You know, when I would open the map and draw on it or something, I would usually play that song.
Yeah.
This is indeed my favorite poop and pee game.
Not that there's many, but yeah.
Rainworld also has good music, true.
But Rainworld has a type of music that just works better while playing.
It doesn't quite stand on its own, I think, outside of the gameplay.
At least not for me.
I can't just sit and listen to Rainworld music all day, you know, same as I can listen to stuff like this.
It's more tuned to the game and what's happening on the screen, I think.
And I really enjoyed the music in Rainworld when I played it, you know?
Oh, Green Path music is also goaded, definitely.
The Rainworld DLC, I think.
I had plans on doing that at some point, but honestly, at this point, I've kind of lost interest in it a little.
Because it's been so long since I played Rainworld, I don't even remember how to play the game.
It's probably gonna be a disaster.
I don't know.
I'm not really feeling it, honestly.
But I'm not gonna say never.
It could happen.
What are your thoughts on Inside?
I love it, Kuroga.
It's one of my all-time favorite small experiences in gaming.
Like, less than four hours, you know?
It is unbelievably beautiful and haunting at the same time.
And it has an incredible soundtrack, and I love the way they play with the music and what's happening on screen as well, you know?
You'll know what I mean if you've played it, especially like a certain section a little later in the game.
Oh, so good.
Why are people writing in non-English languages?
I can't understand that.
Sorry.
I've not played Little Nightmares yet, but I want to.
I heard it's sort of similar to Inside, which is very promising.
So for that reason alone, I'm looking forward to it.
You don't remember any music, Chicadery, Don?
Man, okay, I'm gonna spoil a little bit.
Close your ears if you haven't played the game, okay?
For the next 15 seconds.
The underwater sections, where there's like this thing that pulls you in, and it opens and closes with the music.
That's one part.
The other part is the shake chamber with the blast wave.
The way the music is building up as you approach it, and then it really goes crazy when you're inside.
I think it is unbelievably well done.
It is so memorable.
I don't think any game has done it as well as that game when it comes to that.
More streams, please.
It's been so long.
I'm streaming as much as I can when I have fun.
So there are days when I just don't feel like streaming.
I could go live, but it's just gonna it's just not gonna be super enjoyable for either me or you.
And lately I've just, you know, not really had the need to play as many games.
Which sucks, you know, because it's my job to play games, but it also needs to be enjoyable to watch, which means I have to enjoy it.
So, you know.
I have periods of wanting to play a lot, and then periods of where I don't play that much, and yeah.
The atmosphere, exactly, Kuroga.
The atmosphere is top-notch.
That's the best way to put it, yes.
Find a comparable to Portal in terms of length.
Really?
Oh, you're talking about the first Portal.
I would say the Portal one is a little longer, right?
Wasn't that like five or six hours-ish?
Inside, if I remember correctly, was like three or four.
Would you ever have a night of playing games made by your community?
Maybe even host your own game jam.
I mean, I don't even know how to make games.
And I don't know if I want to play games that are made like over a weekend or something.
I don't think I would find that very enjoyable, if I'm being totally honest.
That's just not really something I enjoy.
I did actually watch Back Rooms Yumu.
I watched it with a friend of mine just a couple days ago.
I thought it was great, but I left the cinema wanting more.
You know, I'm not going to spoil anything, don't worry.
But I was just thinking, man, I want more.
I want to know more.
You know, like they left me hanging on so many things.
I also watched Obsession yesterday, actually.
I went to the cinema alone to watch that.
Holy shit, guys.
Obsession is probably my favorite movie of the year so far.
And it's made by a guy called... what's his name?
Curry Barker, who is a guy that also runs a YouTube channel called...
it's so stupid or something, I forget the name of it.
And he does it with his other guy and they have amazing chemistry and humor.
It's always the funny guys that make the best horror movies.
Obsession is insane, guys.
It made me so uncomfortable, it's crazy.
Like I had involuntary tears streaking from my eyes, not because I was crying, but because of how tense it was and how uncomfortable it was.
I highly recommend it.
Okay, I'm going to have a game jam then of 10 years.
Go make Grand Theft Auto 7 then.
10 year long game jam, guys.
Starting now.
And you have to work on it full time.
I'm just kidding.
I also watched the space movie with... what's his name?
Ryan Gosling.
That was also good.
Although not as good as back rooms or obsession, but still good.
I enjoyed that one too.
It was a nice atmosphere.
I want more sci-fi movies.
Like I'm starving of sci-fi movies.
I feel like the golden age of sci-fi is kind of over, you know?
The 90s and 2000s had so many crazy good sci-fi movies.
I mean, there are sci-fi movies coming out, but a lot of them are just not that good.
Unfortunately.
Okay, I'm out of here, guys.
Thanks for watching.
This was actually very fun.
Successful challenge stream.
Next time we're going to mix it up a bit more and do different things.
And check out the new character that we unlocked.
Of course.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.